find-mba.com 2018-12-19

# Privacy Policy | FIND MBA

At Pritzwalks GmbH & Co. KG, the operator of FIND MBA ([www.find-mba.com](https://find-mba.com/)), (hereinafter referred to as “FIND MBA”) we strive for transparency and trust when it comes to protecting your privacy. In this section, we would like to explain how we collect and process your information. This policy outlines how and why FIND MBA collects and uses various types of behavioral and personal information. When it comes to your personal information, please be reminded that you have the right to access, change or delete your information at any time.

Please read this policy in conjunction with our Cookie Policy and Terms of Use to make sure that you understand how we collect and use your data.

As our privacy policy is updated regularly to reflect changes in legislation and best practice, we advise you to check our latest version from time to time.

**The information we collect**

When you register at FIND MBA, personal information such as your name and e-mail address will be collected via our registration form. We will use this information solely to personalize the content you will see based on your personal preferences and to improve our understanding of our users’ needs in developing FIND MBA. We will not share this information with any third party nor will we allow third parties to send you information to your submitted e-mail address.

While not mandatory, we ask you for certain personal information in order to provide our services. Examples of details we may collect in this context:

  * Username
  * Password
  * E-mail address
  * Name
  * Country
  * Postal address
  * Photo or avatar

If you choose to send an e-mail to one of the listed institutions at FIND MBA by pushing the “Request Information”-button, you consent to receiving information from the chosen institution. The e-mail you send will be identified as coming from your personal e-mail address and not from FIND MBA. However, the e-mail will contain an introductory statement indicating that you have sent this e-mail through our website. Your information may also be stored in FIND MBA's secure system, where it can be accessed only by representatives at the institution from which you requested information.

When you visit FIND MBA, we collect information that helps us deliver our services and improve your user experience. We do so through cookies and other technologies. Here are some examples of the types of information we may collect:

  * Browser
  * E-mail provider
  * Pages that you read on FIND MBA and how you reached them
  * Device
  * IP address
  * Internet connection
  * Location

As part of this process, a cookie will be placed on your hard drive. This file allows you to move quickly and easily around our site. It enables us to identify returning users and identify registrants. As a registrant you will have the cookie linked to your e-mail address so that you will not need to log in each time you visit. We may also use a cookie to track a user's sessions. We only use this information to find out what site features are most popular so that we can develop FIND MBA accordingly. You can delete cookies from your hard drive at any time. However, once the cookie is deleted, any settings such as your stored username and password will have to be re-entered when you log in again.

We do not collect or track sensitive information about our users, such as race, religion, ethnicity, and political opinion. When you register for a user account on FIND MBA, you agree to allow FIND MBA to use the e-mail address that you provided to send you regular newsletters, website status updates, advertising for related products and services, and surveys for internal purposes, unless you opt-out of this service by submitting a request to unsubscribe through FIND MBA's Contact page.

**Why we collect your information**

We use your information for the following reasons:

  * to deliver our services;
  * to maintain and improve our services;
  * to develop new services;
  * to measure user response and user experience;
  * to communicate with you;
  * to prevent users from posting unlawful, offensive or objectionable comments on our site

You have the right to object to our use of your information by contacting us. We will consider your objections and get back to you with a decision in a timely manner.

**How we retain and store your information**

We store your information for as long as we need to in order render our services to you in accordance with applicable law.

We will generally not hold your information for a period longer than 10 years, provided that you do not interact with us or log in to your account during this period. We would only keep your data for longer than this in case we are required to do so by law.

As FIND MBA is visited by users from all over the world, the usage of our website involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Thus, by browsing FIND MBA and communicating electronically with us, you consent to our processing of personal data in this way.

As we work with third parties outside the European Union (EU) and European Economic Area (EEA), we may transfer your personal information internationally, including outside of the EU and the EEA. By accessing our website, you acknowledge and agree to your personal information being transferred in this way.

Information security is important to us and we implement suitable measures to ensure your information remains safe with us, including by limiting who has access to your information.

**Users under 16**

We do not knowingly or intentionally process personal information from users under the age of 16. If a parent or guardian has informed us that such data has been collected by us, we will delete any details of such users from our records.
